to this offseason program. It's a
10-week program starting from today to
June 18th. Okay, we get to start early.
All right, we get to work. We get to
work early. So, it's phase one, it's a
vet mini camp I'll tell you about here
in a second. Phase two, we got nine
OTAAS and a mandatory mini camp. What
we're doing right now, what we're doing
is laying our foundation. Okay, that's
what we're doing right here in this
room. That's what we're doing this week
as we get started. Okay. So, what we
will do in this offseason program is we
will establish a clear identity for our
football team, for our offense, for our
defense, for our special teams. Okay?
The focus of what we do will be on
fundamentals and techniques. Scheme is
fun. X's and O's are fun. I got you. But
we will focus on fundamentals and
techniques because they carry you
through at the end of the day. And then
why we're here, we're under one roof, is
to become a team. Some of that will
happen naturally. Some of that will be
going out to dinner like you did last
night or tonight. Being under one roof,
you got a chance to become a team and
you guys are here and I appreciate that.
We don't have a lot of rules, guys. We
We don't. Okay. So, very very simply,
our standard is do what you're supposed
to do when you're supposed to do it
every time. Do what you're supposed to
do when you're supposed to do it every
time. Pretty simple, right? So, I'm not
going to recite every rule there is in
in football. we just want to do this,
right? That's the standard that we hold
ourselves to. Now, there are
non-negotiables. Being on time, whether,
like Griff said, whether it's in the
weight room, whether it's in here,
whether it's in your meeting rooms,
whatever our first thing that we got
going is, be on time. Obviously, treat
each other with respect. You'll get that
from me, you'll get that from your
coaches. We should get that from each
other. We should get that from this
building. And then protect the team. So,
recap, right? 10-week program, laying
the foundation, establishing a clear
identity, focus on fundamentals and
techniques, become a team. Clear
identity. Clear identity. There's a
great quote. Won't be the last time
you'll hear me say this. Choose your
identity or someone else will choose it
for you. We're choosing our identity
around here. Okay? We are not letting
anybody else choose it for us. You guys
are blessed. I'm blessed to coach the
greatest team game there is. You guys
are blessed to play the greatest team
game. There is, the best.
I want everyone in here to have
incredible individual success, but not
in front of the collective, not in front
of the team. Okay? So, everything that
we do here at the Atlanta Falcons,
everything we do, we will put the team
first. Okay? That's myself included.
That's your coaches. That's this room.
We will put the team first in every
single thing that we do. That's your
identity. That's who we choose to be as
a football team.
So day one, 2026 Atlanta Falcons. If we
want to do something special, if we want
to do something special, we have to
build that foundation. Okay? It's so
easy to talk about the end result. I
could put a picture up here of of the
Lombardi up. I can do it. That is easy.
That easy easy to talk about. The hard
part is what you're what you're getting
ready to do today. Okay? being here
today, what you're gonna do in the
weight room today, how you're going to
push each other today, your expectations
of what today, that leads to that
special thing. Okay? So, we won't focus
on what's out there way down the line.
We're going to focus on what's in front
of us today. And that's building a great
foundation for 2026. All right? All
right. Let's break it up.